Finding aid for the Experiments in Art and Technology records, 1966-1993 (bulk 1966-1973)
Experiments in Art and Technology records
- Audio tapes, 1966-1993; Series VII.; ca. 8.5 lin. ft. 13 boxes
  Series VII contains 107 reel-to-reel and 138 cassette tapes arranged in rough chronological order. Events recorded include "9 Evenings" sounds used in the performances, recordings of some performances (copies of Tudor and Cage) and interviews with engineers and artists; Pavilion sounds used as input material for the sound system, Tudor's first 4-track recording of works made for the Pavilion, interviews with participants and meetings; E.A.T. lecture-demonstration series; meetings, interviews and material from other E.A.T. projects; and Klüver lectures and talks.
  Missing lecture tapes:
  155. Apr 2, 1980
  156. Jun 20, 1976, Paris
  157. 9 Evenings speech draft Jan 13, 1980
  158. 9 Evenings at the Kitchen Jan 30, 1980
  Originals housed in boxes 220-232. Reformatted copies are described below with the originals, but shelved elsewhere. E.A.T. staff numbered the audio tapes and copied many of the 7 in. reel-to-reel tapes onto cassettes (see below the reel-to-reel tapes). Run times provided by the reformatter.
  - "9 Evenings," (Reel-to-reel tapes), 1966
    - Alfons Schilling, Hay and Whitman interviews (Reel R1)
      1 sound tape reel (30 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Begins with Alfons Schilling and Whitman on telephone. Whitman's end disappears. Deborah Hay and Schilling. Label on reel: "reject, Debby"; label on box: "9 eves, Begins w Schilling & Whitman on telephone..." [See also C1]
      1 sound tape reel (30 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (30 min., 30 sec.) Copy master.
    - Material for Schilling film on 9 Evenings, 1 of 4 (Reel R2)
      1 sound tape reel (23 min.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      labels on reel: "no. 1" and "transferred JS NE 1 2-21-67" and "re-transferred 3-7-67 JS." Label on box: "Material for A. Schilling film on 9 eves..." [See also C2]
      1 sound tape reel (23 min.): analog; 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (23 min.): digital. Copy master.
    - Material for Schilling film on 9 Evenings, 2 of 4 (Reel R3)
      1 sound tape reel (25 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. N.B., recorded on Side 1 only, right track.
      Labels on reel: "no. 2" and "transferred JS NE 2 2-21-67" and "re-transferred 3-7-67." Label on box: "Material for A. Schilling film on 9 eves...." [See also C3]
      1 sound tape reel (25 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (25 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Material for Schilling film on 9 Evenings, 3 of 4 (Reel R4)
      1 sound tape reel (35 min., 36 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Side 1: no label; Side 2: "No. 3" and "Transferred JS NE 3 2-21-67." On box: "Clean" and "3 of 3." [See also C4]
      1 sound reel (35 min., 36 sec.): analog, mono.; 71/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (35 min., 36 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Material for Schilling film on 9 Evenings, 4 of 4 (Reel R5)
      1 sound tape reel (28 min.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Labels on reel: "no. 4" and "transferred JS NE 2 2-21-67" and "re-transferred 3-7-67 JS." Label on box: "Material for A. Schilling film on 9 eves...." [See also C5]
      1 sound tape reel (28 min.): analog; 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (28 min.): digital. Copy master.
    - Alex Hay interview with Schilling (Reel R6)
      1 sound tape reel (44 min.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: " Alex out, good tape" On box: "Alex Hay." [See also C6]
      1 sound tape reel (44 min.): analog; 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (44 min.): digital. Copy master.
    - Alex Hay sound from performance (Reel R7)
      1 sound tape reel (10 min.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "No 14 Alex Hay"; on box: "Alex Hay, Clean, Schilling." [See also C7]
      1 sound tape reel (10 min.): analog; 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (10 min.): digital. Copy master.
    - Interview with Steve Paxton, 1971 Nov 15 (Reel R8)
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 2 min., 18 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "1 3/4 speed interview w/ Steve Paxton 11-5-71." [See also C8]
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (2 hr., 2 min., 18 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs (CDs) (2 hr., 2 min., 18 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Steve Paxton: Greta Garbo, Debbie Drake, undated (Reel R9)
      1 sound tape reel (3 hr., 9 min., 59 sec.): analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "CH 1 Greta Garbo CH 2 Debby Drake 3 3/4 PAXTON." [See also C9]
      3 sound tape reels of 3 (3 hr., 9 min., 59 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      3 sound discs of 3 (CDs) (3 hr., 9 min., 59 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Strange Wills, radio program, Steve Paxton, undated (Reel R10)
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 26 min., 38 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Paxton 7 1.2 Mono Strange Wills Episode 59 part 1 Episode 60 part 1." [See also C10]
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 26 min., 38 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (2 hr., 26 min., 38 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Steve Paxton short sound: program on Native American field hockey, undated, 1966? (Reel R11)
      1 sound tape reel (2 min., 18 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Written on post-it note in box: "Paxton sound 9 eves beginning most reel empty."
      1 sound tape reel (2 min., 18 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (2 min., 18 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Loop tapes: "The Avengers (radio drama) / Tschudin, Electric Raga in E, undated (Reel R12)
      1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 3 min., 49 sec.): analog, mono. 7 in. Original.
      Cardboard and plastic 3-D glasses included. Label on side 1: "No. 11 Fahlström." Written on box: "2 Electric Raga in E 111," and "12." [See also C12]
      1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 3 min., 49 sec.): analog, mono. 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (1 hr., 3 min., 49 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Steve Paxton: Stop Smoking, Isometric Exercising, John Glenn, 1966 Sep 8 (Reel R13)
      1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 35 min., 39 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Paxton Stop Smoking Isometrics John Glenn," and "Sept 8, 1966 1. Stop Smoking side 1 + 2 2. Isometric Exercising side 1 + 2 3. John Glenn side 1 + 2." [See also C13]
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (1 hr., 35 min., 39 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (1 hr., 35 min., 39 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Funakakushi-1 and interview [with Toshi Ichiyanagi?], originally recorded labelled, 1963 Mar 6, 1966 Sep 20 (Reel R14)
      1 sound tape reel (18 min., 30 sec.): mono and stereo, analog; 7 in. Original.
      Funakakushi-1 (stereo, 13 min.), interview in Japanese (mono, 4 min.). Label on reel: "transferred NE4, JS, 2-21-67" and label on box: "Funakakush-1, Toshi Ichiyanagi,... 9/20/66." [See also C14?]
      1 sound tape reel (18 min., 30 sec.): mono and stereo, analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (18 min., 30 sec.): digital. Copy master.
    - David Tudor "Bandoneon" [sic] (Reel R15)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono. 7 in. Original.
      Labelled on box: "Cut 1-Bandoneon, Cut 2- Bandoneon, Cut 3- Bandoneon, Tudor, Schilling." Label on edge of box: "David Tudor, 9 eves, 1966." Tape actually contains sound track recording of a show called "Nurses" - nothing to do with 9 evenings, etc. Not reformatted.
    - Voice of America French service on 9 evenings, with Öyvind Fahlström interview (Reel R17)
      1 sound tape reel (8 min., 43 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 3/4 ips, 5 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "Armory show." Label on box: "Reportage in French on 'Theatre and engineering' including interview with Oyvino Fahlström... ." Note in box: "Interview in French with Fahlström." [See also C17]
      1 sound tape reel (8 min., 43 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (8 min., 43 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Beethoven Tape record #4 (Reel R18)
      Label on reel: "IV Beeth." Label on box: "Tape rec. #4 (Beethoven)...."
      1 sound tape reel (5 min., 34 sec): analog, mono.; 5 in. Original.
      1 sound tape reel (5 min., 34 sec): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (5 min., 34 sec): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Interviews with Öyvind Fahlström (21 min.) and Yvonne Rainer (19 min.) (Reel R19)
      1 sound tape reel (40 min): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "reject Öyvind, bad tape...." Label on box: "93: interview with Yvonne R., Öyvind F...." [See also C26a?]
      1 sound tape reel (40 min): analog, mono.; 7 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (40 min): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Fahlström call to Shanghai for 9 Evenings (Reel R20)
      1 sound tape reel (8 min., 30 sec.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Extremely poor sound, could not be improved in reformatting. Label on reel: "Shanghai." Label on box: "Fahlström call to Shanghai for 9E." [See also C20-C22]
      1 sound tape reel (8 min., 30 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (8 min., 30 sec.): digital. Copy master.
    - Fine and You? (Reel R21)
      1 sound tape reel (12 min., 38 sec.): analog, stereo; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Original.
      Contains 2 recordings of "Fine and you?" - each 6 min., 19 sec. Label on box: "7 1/2 ips stereo...13 min, side A only." On leader: "Fine - and you? (2 copies)." [See also C20-C22]
      1 sound tape reel (12 min., 38 sec.): analog, stereo; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (12 min., 38 sec.): digital, stereo. Copy master.
    - Fahlström piece (Reel R22)
      1 sound tape reel (33 min.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "Out, Brando, 9 evenings." Label on box: "Fahlström piece." Recording (on Side 1 only) of sound from a movie on TV. Does not pertain to Fahlström piece. Not reformatted.
    - Öyvind Fahlström: short piece of speech, undated (Reel R23)
      1 sound tape reel (54 min., 25 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 5/16 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Written on box: "Mono 1 5/16 ips Side A only." [See also C23]
      1 sound tape reel (54 min., 25 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (54 min., 25 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Öyvind Fahlström #1 (Reel R24)
      1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. Original.
      Labels on reel: "Tails out," and "Tape 12.25 Fahlström." Label on box: "Öyvind Fahlström.. .Schilling." No notes from reformatter.
      1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD): digital. Copy master.
    - Öyvind Fahlström #2 [sic] (Reel R25)
      1 sound tape reel (ca. 2 min.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "No. 12 Fahlström." Label on box: "Fahlström...Öyvind, A) B axton...B) Ch. George...C) ...Schilling." Label on edge of box: "Öyvind Fahlström #2, 9 eves 1966." Contains voice tests (1 1/2 min.), someone dictating a letter (30 sec.) and silence. Not reformatted.
    - Öyvind Fahlström #3 (Reel R26)
      1 sound tape reel (32 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "No. 15 Fahlström." On box: "Öyvind, ... Schilling." On edge of box: Öyvind Fahlström #3, 9 eves 1966."
      1 sound tape reel (32 min.): analog, mono.; 71/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (32 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Bob Whitman interviewed by Simone (Whitman) Forti about 9 evenings, 1966 Mar 27 (Reel R27)
      1 sound tape reel (42 min.): analog, mono; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "9 evenings, 1966" and "Bob Whitman interviewed by Simone (Whitman) Forti." On box: "3/27/66, interview Bob Whitman, 9 evenings T & E, by Simone Forti." On edge of box: "Interview with B. Whitman 3/27/66." [See also C27]
      1 sound tape reel (42 min.): analog, mono; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (42 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Simone Whitman interview fragments, 1966 (Reel R28)
      1 sound tape reel (28 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Right track contains fragments of Simone Whitman (Forti) interviews. Left track contains 2 min. of children playing, then short cut of a beginning segment from the right track. Remainder of left track is blank. Varying sound quality.
      Label on reel: "Fragments from interviews Simone Whitman." On edge of box: "S. Whitman - Interview fragments 1966."
      Includes 3 pages of manuscript notes. [See also C28]
      1 sound tape reel (28 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (28 min., 30 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Robert Whitman, 9 evenings, 1966 (Reel R29)
      1 sound tape reel (32 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "No. 2 Whitman." On box: "Whitman, no good,...sound from Whitman,...Schilling." On edge of box: "R. Whitman - 9 eves 1966." [See also C29]
      1 sound tape reel (32 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (32 min., 30 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Lucinda Childs, 9 evenings, 1966 (Reel R30)
      1 sound tape reel (11 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Side 1: Sonar Movement Sound; Side 2: poorly recorded radio show, not related to Childs -Station KEA 860. Only side 1 reformatted. Label on box: "Lucinda Childs, 245 Church street, N.Y. 10013..." On edge of box: "Lucinda Childs 9 eves 1966." Includes 2 pp. manuscript notes. [See also C30]
      1 sound tape reel (11 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (11 min., 30 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Lucinda Child's first performance, 1966 (Reel R31)
      1 sound tape reel (18 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "No. 2 Lucinda Childs." On box: "Lucinda Childs, 1st performance...Schilling." On edge of box: "Lucinda Childs, 9 eves 1966." [See also C31]
      1 sound tape reel (18 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (18 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - 18 Names - from Rauschenberg's opening scene (Reel R32)
      1 sound tape reel (30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Tape contains only 30 sec. of sound - 18 artists say "I am..." and then their names. Label on box: "A few names." On edge of box: "From Rauschenberg's opening scene? 18 names...." Not reformatted. [See C32]
    - L.J. Robinson interview, 1966 Sep 14 (Reel R38)
      1 sound tape reel (53 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "Backwards!" and "Robinson 9-14-66." [See also C38]
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (53 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (53 min.): analog, mono. Copy master.
  - Pepsi Pavilion, other projects, meetings, and symposia, (Reel-to-reel tapes), 1967-1970
    - David Tudor sounds for Pepsi Pavilion, some voices, wind sounds, ca. 1970? (Reel R48)
      1 sound tape reel: analog. Original. Not reformatted.
    - Bob Breer, 1967 Mar 3 (Reel R49)
      Tape recorded on 1 side only and so low in volume, reformatter could not save. Label on box: "Bob Breer 3/3/67."Not reformatted.
    - Pepsi-Cola Co. presents "The Route Salesman's Job" (Reel R50)
      1 sound tape reel (10 min., plus): analog, mono. 7 in. Original
      Sound track for a slide show. The "clicks" on the sound track are for the slide projectionist to change to the next slide. This runs for 10 minutes. This is followed by music tracks from the slide show tape.
      1 sound tape reel (10 min., plus): analog, mono. 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (10 min., plus): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - David Tudor Pavilion (Reel R51)
      Tape missing (not received from E.AT.). Not reformatted.
    - Biologics, 1993? (Reel R57)
      1 sound tape reel (22 minutes): analog, mono; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "abt. 1 min. at begin of 'Biologics.'" Label on box back: "Biologics, 12/93, empty tape." Label on box spine: "Biologics."
      1 sound tape reel (22 minutes): analog, mono; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (22 minutes): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Pauline Oliveros, Lynn Lonidier interview reel no. 1, 1968 Jul 18 (Reel R59)
      1 sound tape reel (30 min., 49 sec.): analog, mono.; 5 in. Original. [See also C59 (?)]
      1 sound tape reel (30 min., 49 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (30 min., 49 sec.): digital, moni. Copy master.
    - Nilo Lundgren interview with Larry Owens #2, 1969 (Reel R66)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono. Original.
      [Masters and use copy made from cassettes, C65-C66, Feb 1998. Reel-to-reel tape not reformatted.]
    - Nilo Lundgren interview with Billy Klüver, 1970 Jan 8 (Reel R72)
      2 sound tape reels of 2: analog, mono.; 7 in. Original
      [Masters and use copy made from cassette original Feb 1998. See C72. Reel-to-reel tapes not reformatted.]
    - Homage to E.A.T., Fred, Robby, Billy dinner at the YMHA, 1967 Feb 18 (Reel R78)
      1 sound tape reel (ca. 2 hr., 16 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. [Recorded on Side 1 only.][See also C78]
      4 sound tape reels of 4 (ca. 2 hr., 16 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CD) (ca. 2 hr., 16 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - WBAI talk, first version, 1967 Jun 28 (Reel R79)
      1 sound tape reel (50 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. [See also C79]
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (50 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (50 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Francis Mason interview, Corcoran Gallery, Washington D.C., 1968 May 13 (Reel R80)
      Label on box: "Voice of America...Intv. Francis Mason, President, Experiments in Art & Technology...Corcoran Gallery - May 13, 1968."
      1 sound tape reel (8 min., 55 sec.): analog, mono.: 7 in. Original.
      1 sound tape reel (8 min., 55 sec.): analog, mono.: 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (8 min., 55 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Art and Technology Symposium, Corcoran Gallery, Washington D.C., #1, 1968 May 13 (Reel R81)
      Label on box: "Voice of America...Symposium: Art and Technology, Corcoran Gallery, May 13, 1968, Reel 1."
      1 sound tape reel (32 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
    - Art and Tech Symposium, Corcoran #2, May 13, 1968 (Reel R82)
      Label on box: "Voice of America...Symposium: Art and Technology, Corcoran Gallery, May 13, 1968, Reel 2."
      1 sound tape reel (34 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      1 sound tape reel (34 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (34 min., 30 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Art and Tech Symposium, Corcoran #3, May 13, 1968 (Reel R83)
      Label on box: "Voice of America...Symposium: Art and Technology, Corcoran Gallery, May 13, 1968, Reel 3."
      1 sound tape reel (13 min., 20 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      1 sound tape reel (13 min., 20 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (13 min., 20 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Discussion: artist project involving ring counter and voice-activated mike, Claudio Badal, W.G. Leeman, Bob Allerot, Tony Tedona (Reel R84)
      Label on box back: "Cladio - Newsletter info, W.G. Leeman, Bob Allerot, Tony Tedona..." On box spine: "Disc artist project, ring counter, voice activated mike." Side 1 only.
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      2 sound tape reels of 2: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Shaker Village / Jerry Marks interview, 1965 (Reel R85)
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 35 min., 45 sec.): analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original
      Label on box back: "Shaker Village Work Group, Shaker Service 1965..." On box spine: "Shaker Village." Inserted card has pencil notes: "printed circuits, chemistry of ink,..."
      First few minutes are an explanation of the silk screen process. The second part is of the Shaker Village Group performing. Final parts are of the Shaker Service. Volume flux throughout on original and reformatted versions. Chief recording engineers: Mark Sandler and Rick Abrams, S.V.W.G.; Jerry Marks interview. [See also C85 for Marks interview]
      4 sound tape reels of 4 (2 hr., 35 min., 45 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master
      3 sound disc of 3 (2 hr., 35 min., 45 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Interview between Tracy Kinsel, engineer, and John Anthes, artist, who collaborated on an E.A.T. project (Reel R86)
      1 sound tape reel (21 min., 39 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Recording of a telephone call from New York City to Providence, R.I. Interview for E.A.T. News. Label on box: "Tracy Kinsel, John Anthes, E.A.T." [See also C86]
      1 sound tape reel (21 min., 39 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (21 min., 39 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - E.A.T. Local group conference #1, 1968 Jun 22 (Reel R87)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: Reel No.1, EAT Local Group conf., 6/22, 1968." [See also C87]
      7 sound tape reels of 7: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      7 sound discs of 7 (CDs): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - E.A.T. Local Group conference #2, 1968 Jun 22-23 (Reel R88)
      Label on box: Reel no. 2, EAT Local Group conf., 6/22, 6/23, 1968." [See also C88]
      5 sound tape reels of 5: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      5 sound discs of 5 (CDs): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - E.A.T. Local Group conference #3, 1968 Jun 24 (Reel R89)
      Label on box: "Reel no. 3, EAT Local Group conf., 6/24, 1968." [See also C89]
      4 sound tape reels of 4: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      4 sound discs of 4 (CDs): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - AAAS meeting Dallas, Tx #1, 1968 Dec 26-31 (Reel R90)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; variable speed, 7 in. Original.
      Label reel: "Side 1, reel 1, Klüver, Garmire, Whitman, Nolan." Label on reel: "Side 2, reel 1, Kepes, Panel disc, ?s frm floor." Label on box: "AAAS meeting from E.A.T. Reel 1, Dec 26-31, 1968, Dallas." [See also C90]
      4 sound reels of 4: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
    - AAAS meeting Dallas, Tx #2, 1968 Dec 26-31 (Reel R91)
      Label on box: "AAAS meeting from E.A.T. reel 2, Dec. 26-31, 1968, Dallas." Reel is incomplete, sound ends abruptly on side 1. [See also C91]
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
    - Alvin Lucier - demonstration tape for his E.A.T. program proposal for Expo '70 (Reel R92)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, stereo; 7 in. Original.
      Part 1: Speech Recycling, Reinforcement of Resonant Frequencies. Electronic Studio Room, Brandeis University. Part 2: Acoustic orientation by means of echo - location. Four performers with sondols. Rose Art Museum, Brandeis. Recorded with environears binaural system.
      1 sound tape reel: analog, stereo; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD): digital, stereo. Copy master.